[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Speaker 1: Hi, thank you for calling PetSmart Customer Care.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] This is Michaela speaking who I have the pleasure of speaking with today.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Speaker 2: Yes, thank you, Michaela.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] My name is Alan.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: Hi, Alan.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] How are you?
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: Very well.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Thank you, South.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: I'm fine.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] What's going on today, Alan?
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: I just need to cancel an order because I just picked up the food from my local Pet Smart.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] I have the order.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: Can I have your phone number and email?
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] I'll just real quick to verify your account, please.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: Yeah, for sure.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Phone number is 647-724-5477.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Email address is Maurizio underscore VT at iCloud.com.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: Thank you so much, Mr.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Allen.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Give me just a moment while I check out this order.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: Thank you.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: Was this the order that was placed on the 30th?
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: That is correct.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: Okay, Alan, unfortunately, this order cannot be canceled as it is too late.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] But what you can do is once the order is delivered, you can return it in store if you would like.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: Okay.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: Okay.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] I will just like, yeah.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Okay, perfect.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] I can do that.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Thank you so much, Michaela.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: No problem.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Is there anything else I can assist you at the moment, Mr.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Alan?
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: No, that's everything.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Thank you.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Have a good night.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: You as well.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Thank you for calling Pet Smart.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Take care.